{
  "response_code": 0,
  "results": [
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Music",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Rapper Snoop Dogg's real name is 'Cordozar Calvin Broadus, Jr.'.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Music",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Norwegian producer Kygo released a remix of the song \"'Sexual Healing\"' by Marvin Gaye.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Music",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Ashley Frangipane performs under the stage name Halsey.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Music",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "For his performance at ComplexCon 2016 in Long Beach, California, Skrillex revived his \"'Mothership\"' set piece for one night only.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Music",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "3 members of 2 Live Crew were arrested for playing songs from their album, As Nasty As They Wanna Be, live.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Music",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Pink Guy's debut album was \"'Pink Season\"'.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Music",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Dave Grohl recorded the Foo Fighters' debut, \"'Foo Fighters,\"' by himself.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Music",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A Facebook campaign placed Rage Against The Machine's \"'Killing in the Name Of\"' as the UK Christmas Number 1 in 2009.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Music",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Metallica collaborated with Rowan Atkinson's Mr Bean on a 1992 comic relief single.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Music",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Green Day's album 'American Idiot' is considered a \"'punk rock opera.\"'",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    }
  ]
}